<book title="Hello friend!">
    <chapter>
        <page>
            <title align="center">Welcome friend!</title>
            <p align="center"><image src="atb:cover" tw="100" th="100"/></p>
            <p>This modpack was made for you with love. Enclosed in this book are some things to keep in mind.</p>
        </page>
        <page>
            <title>Table of Contents</title>
            <p><link ref="1:day1">First Day</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:jei">JEI</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:map">Map</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:death">Graves and Death</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:skills">Class and Skill Tree</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:food">Food</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:mons">Monster Girls</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:shaders">Enabling Shaders</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:backpack">Backpack</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:seasons">Seasons</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:agriculture">Agriculture</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:baubles">Baubles</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:bop">Biomes and Compass</link></p>
            <p><link ref="1:carry">Carry Stuff</link></p>
            <p><link ref="recipes">Skill Book Recipies</link></p>
        </page>
    </chapter>
    <chapter>
		<page>
			<title>Skillbook Recipies</title>
            <p>All the new items and activies can be pretty overwhelming. To get started, grab one of the guidebooks from the starting room, or craft your own.</p>
            <p></p>
            <p>Learning one mod at a time can help keep you from getting overwhelmed by all the new content.</p>
            <p><link ref="recipes">Skill Book Recipies</link></p>
        </page>
		<page id="day1">
			<title>First Day</title>
            <p>There's a whole lot of new stuff to explore. Look around!</p>
            <p>We've provided you with a bedroll so you can rest on your travels. You can make a campfire to cook food on the go. A lot of wild food can be found.</p>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="campfire:campfire_recipe"></recipe>
        </page>
        <page id="jei">
            <title>JEI - Just Enough Items</title>
            <p>If you open your inventory and look to the right, you'll se an outrageous number of items. This is JEI and it's your new best friend. You can search for recipies here!</p>
            <p>Use the searchbar to search for blocks. Use @blank to search by mod, and $blank to search by ore dict entrry.</p>
        </page>
        <page id="map">
            <title>Journey Map</title>
            <p>Press J to pull up your map. Here you can view and set waypoints as well as see where you've been. The diamond shaped button in the lower left hand corner is your waypoints.</p>
            <p>You can set coordinates for your own custom waypoints as well.</p>
        </page>
		<page id="death">
			<title>Graves and Death</title>
			<p>When you die you will leave a grave behind, as well as a marker in Journey Map. Sneak over this grave to reclaim your items. Equipped items will go back into slosts.</p>
			<p>You also recieve a list of items you had on death.</p>
			<p>Grave markers can be cleared in JourneyMap under waypoints by removing the waypoint.</p>
		</page>
        <page id="skills">
            <title>Skills Trees and Classes</title>
            <p>You spawn with a skillbook. If you die you can craft another one.</p>
            <p>You can use this book to choose a starting class and distribute skill points.</p>
            <p>Your first class determines what you will recieve bonus XP in: Combat, Mining, or Crafting.</p>
        </page>
        <page>
            <p>You can also get some starting bonuses for it.</p>
            <p>Investing skill points into a tree costs 5 experience levels. You keep your skills on death.</p>
        </page>
		<page id="food">
			<title>Nutrition, Food, and Cooking</title>
			<p>Nutrition matters now. Press "N" or click on the carrot button in your inventory to bring up your nutrition stats.</p>
			<p>Keeping your nutrition from dropping too low is important, because at low levels you may experience the "Miner's Fatigue" debuff.</p>
        </page>
        <page>
			<p>If you keep your nutrition levels high, you can recieve various buffs, such as Strength or Toughness. Building up a tolerance to spicy food can lead you to resist fire damage!</p>
			<p></p>
			<p>Additionally, eating a variety of food matters more now. Eating the same food over and over will have diminishing returns.</p>
        </page>
        <page>
            <p>Eating new foods can lead to a permanent increase in your health bar.</p>
			<p>There are lots of new crops and recipies to try out. Build a kitchen with Cooking for Blockheads to experiment.</p>
		</page>
        <page id="mons">
            <title>Monster Girls</title>
            <p>We have added in a lot of new monster girls. Some are friendly, some are less. Hey, if you're a sub, you'll probably be into it.</p>
            <p>Passive mobs from Grimoire of Gaia can be tamed with some Monster Feed. Monster Feed can be made with quality meals or alchohol.</p>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="crafttweaker:monster0"/>
        </page>
        <page>
            <p>If you are attacked in the vicinity of a tamed monster girl, she will fight with you. (Iron golemn AI)</p>
			<p></p>
            <p>Hostile Grimoire of Gaia mobs can also be made non-hostile. If you feed her some Premium Monster Feed, she will be passive towards you for a while.</p>
            <!--<recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="grimoireofgaia:food_monster_feed_premium"/>-->
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="crafttweaker:monster5"/>
        </page>
		<page id="shaders">
			<title>Enabling Shaders</title>
			<p align="center" color="#606060">"RTX on!"</p>
			<p>To make Minecraft look hella good, go into Options > Video settings > Shaders. We have pre-loaded a couple for you to try out. Jakob likes Sildur's High. Experiment and see which options you like best. You can also download your own and install locally by putting them in the Shaders folder.</p>
        </page>
        <page>
			<p>To get bump maps and reflective textures, go into Resource Packs and select one with advanced materials. We have pre-loaded Vanilla PBR and AVPBR, but you can find others online. Make sure to turn on the "Advanced Materials" setting in your Shaders settings.</p>
		</page>
		<page id="backpack">
			<title>Traveler's Backpack</title>
			<p>You can make a backpack to hold an extra inventory's worth of stuff. It also can cointain tanks for fluids, a crafting table, and a bedroll!</p>
			<p>Sleeping in a bedroll does not move your spawn point.</p>
			<recipe key="travelersbackpack:travelers_backpack_standard"></recipe>
		</page>
		<page>
			<title id="seasons">Seasons and Agriculture</title>
			<p>Seasons have been brought to Minecraft. You can watch the leaves turn colors and snow come to biomes that normally don't see it.</p>
			<p>Not all crops can grow in all seasons. You can grow underground or in a greenhouse to tolerate the changing weather, however.</p>
        </page>
        <page id="agriculture">
			<p>Many crops and trees can be achieved using cross-breeding. Check out <link ref="recipes:agricraft">Agricraft</link> to get started with breeding stronger crops, and creating new ones.</p>
			<p>New foods can be found by breaking gardens. Turn these into seeds in your crafting menu, or cook them into delicious new foods.</p>
        </page>
        <page>
			<p>To breed new trees, flowers, and resource bees, check out <link ref="recipes:forestry">Forestry</link>.</p>
			<p>Animals have also been made more complex and interesting. They have to be kept happy to produce resources, and most can only be milked when nursing. Check out <link ref="recipes:animania">Animania</link> to get into animal husbandry.</p>
		</page>
        <page id="baubles">
            <title>Baubles</title>
            <p>Your inventory has a new addition to it. Click the circle next to your armour to bull up your equipped baubles.</p>
            <p>Several mods add items to equip here, like magic rings, toolbelts, or elytra.</p>
        </page>
        <page id="bop">
            <title>Biomes and Nature's Compass</title>
            <p>A lot of new biomes to explore have been added.</p>
            <p>You can craft Nature's Compass to see which ones you haven't visited yet, or find the nearest one.</p>
            <recipe key="naturescompass:natures_compass"></recipe>
        </page>
        <page id="carryon">
            <title>Carrying blocks and animals</title>
            <p>You can carry small animals and some blocks (such as chests or anvils)</p>
            <p>Hold left shift (by default) with an empty hand and right click on the entity to pick it up and move it.</p>
        </page>
    </chapter>
	<chapter id="recipes">
        <page>
        <title>Skillbooks</title>
            <p bold="true">Engineering</p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:tcon1">Tinker's Construct</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:ie">Engineer's Manual</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:comp">Open Computers Manual</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:xnet">Xnet manual</link></p>
                <!--<p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:nuke">Nuclearcraft Guide</link></p>-->
			<p bold="true">Magic</p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:wiz">Wizard's Handbook</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:roots">Druidic Arts</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:witch">Book of Shadows</link></p>
        </page>
        <page>
			<p bold="true">Agriculture</p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:agricraft">Agricultural Journal</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:animania">Animania Manual</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:forestry">Forester's Manual</link></p>
			<p bold="true">Adventure</p>
				<p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:twilight">Traveler's Logbook</link></p>
			<p bold="true">General</p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:bestiary">Universal Bestiary</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:sol">Spice of Life</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:skills">Level Up! Skill Tree Book</link></p>
                <p indent="5">- <link ref="recipes:tome">Akashic Tome</link></p>
		</page>
        <page id="tcon1">
            <title>Tinker's Construct</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="tconstruct:common/book"/>
            <p>Useful for blueprints, and for learning about Tinker's Construct tools and materials</p>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="conarm:book"/>
            <p>For armor</p>
        </page>
        <page id="ie">
            <title>Immersive Engineering</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="immersiveengineering:tool/manual"/>
        </page>
        <page id="comp">
            <title>Open Computers</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="opencomputers:tool58"/>
        </page>
        <page id="xnet">
            <title>XNet</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="xnet:xnet_manual"/>
        </page>
        <!-- Sorry nuclearcraft, your naming conventions are shit so you must be commented out
        <page id="nuke">
            <title>Nuclearcraft</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="nuclearcraft:item.patchouli:guide_book"/>
        </page> -->
        <page id="wiz">
            <title>Wizardry</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="ebwizardry:wizard_handbook"/>
        </page>
        <page id="roots">
            <title>Roots: Druidcraft</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="roots:guide"/>
        </page>
        <page id="witch">
            <title>Bewitchment</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="bewitchment:book_of_shadows"/>
        </page>
        <page id="agricraft">
            <title>Agricraft</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="agricraft:journal"/>
            <p>Keep track of your seeds and mutations</p>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="agricraft:seed_analyzer"/>
            <p>Use to record findings in your Agriculture Journal</p>
        </page>
        <page id="animania">
            <title>Animania</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="animania:animania_manual"/>
            <p>Get started with animal husbandry</p>
        </page>
        <page id="forestry">
            <title>Forestry</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="forestry:book_butterfly"/>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="forestry:book_tree"/>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="forestry:book_honey"/>
        </page>
        <page id="twilight">
            <title>Twilight Forest</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="twilightforest:patchouli_logbook"/>
        </page>
        <page id="bestiary">
            <title>Universal Bestiary</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="universalbestiary:bestiary"/>
        </page>
        <page id="sol">
            <title>Nutrition</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="solcarrot:food_book"/>
        </page>
        <page id="skills">
            <title>Level Up!</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="levelup2:leveling_book"/>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="levelup2:respec_book"/>
        </page>
        <page id="tome">
            <title>Akashic Tome</title>
            <recipe type="gbook:crafting" key="akashictome:tome_1"/>
            <p>Too many skillbooks? Keep them all in this one!</p>
            <p>Or put them all on a bookshelf...</p>
        </page>
    </chapter>
</book>